Finding Aid for the Delmore Schwartz Papers LSC.1005
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Books from the library of Delmore Schwartz
  - Reuben, Reuben. New York: Bantam Books, 1965, Call number: PS3507.E8673 R4 1965 (Box 19)
  - Bullet proof. New York: Popular Library, 1960, Call number: PS3507.E1623 B85 1960 (Box 19)
  - Moll Flanders with a new introduction by Samuel K. Workman. New York: Collier Books, 1962, Call number: PR3404.M6 1962 (Box 1)
  - Robinson Crusoe with an afterword by Harvey Swados. New York: New American Library, 1961, Call number: PR3403.A1 1961 (Box 1)
  - Cranach. New York: H.N. Abrams, 1961, Call number: ND588.C8 D453 (Box 17)
  - Only on Tuesdays. New York: Dell, 1964, Call number: PS3507.E97 (Box 32)
  - Twilight of honor. [New York]: New American Library, 1963, Call number: PS3554.E93 T8 1963 (Box 26)
  - Klee: a study of his life and work translated from the Italian by Stuart Hood. New York: Praeger, 1964, Call number: ND588.K5 S26 1964 (Box 69)
  - Dombey and son with an afterword by Alan Pryce-Jones; with a revised and updated bibliography. New York: New American Library, 1964, Call number: PR4559.A1 1964 (Box 1)
  - Bleak house with an afterword by Geoffrey Tillotson. New York: New American Library, 1964, Call number: PR4556.A1 1964 (Box 34)
  - Hard times: for these times with an afterword by Charles Shapiro. New York: New American Library, 1961, Call number: PR4561.A2 F57 1961 (Box 34)
  - Martin Chuzzlewit with an afterword by Marvin Mudrick. New York: New American Library, 1965, Call number: PR4563.A1 1965 (Box 34)
  - Mystery of Edwin Drood with an afterword by James Wright. New York: New American Library, 1961, Call number: PR4564.A1 1961 (Box 34)
  - Our mutual friend with an afterword by J. Hillis Miller. New York: New American Library, 1964, Call number: PR4568.A1 1964 (Box 34)
  - Personal history, adventures, experience & observations of David Copperfield, the younger of Blunderstone Rookery (which he never meant to be published on any account) with an afterword by Edgar Johnson. New York: New American Library, 1962, Call number: PR4558.A1 1962 (Box 34)
  - Pickwick papers with an afterword by Steven Marcus. New York: New American Library, 1964, Call number: PR4569.A1 1964 (Box 34)
  - Great expectations with an afterword by Angus Wilson. New York: New American Library, 1963, Call number: PR4560.A1 1963 (Box 40)
  - Run River. New York: Bantam, 1964, Call number: PS3554.I33 R86 1964 (Box 18)
  - Winter's tales. New York: Vintage Books, 1942, Call number: PR6003.L545 V513 1942 (Box 19)
  - Find the woman: a mystery. New York: Popular Library, 1964, Call number: PS3507.I75 F56 1964 (Box 17)
  - Confessor. New York: New American Library, 1964, Call number: PS3554.O4673 C6 1964 (Box 40)
  - Ginger man. New York: Berkley Pub. Corp., 1965, Call number: PZ4.D6844 G5 (Box 1)
  - Ginger man. New York: Berkley Pub. Corp., 1964, Call number: PS3507.D684g 1964 (Box 42)
  - Bertrand Russell; a short guide to his philosophy. London, New York: published for the British Council By Longmans, Green, 1951, Call number: B1649.R91 Z7do (Box 12)
  - Mid-century. Boston: Houghton Mifflin, 1961, Call number: PS3507.O743 M5 1961 (Box 29)
  - U.S.A. Illustrated by Reginald Marsh. Boston: Houghton Mifflin, 1963, Call number: PS3507.D74u 1963 (Box 32)
  - Brothers Karamazov translated by Constance Garnett; edited and with a foreword by Manuel Komroff. New York: New American Library, 1957, Call number: PG3326.B7 1957 (Box 7)
  - Brothers Karamazov translated by Constance Garnett. New York: The Modern Library, 1929, Call number: PG3326.B7 (Box 28)
  - Crime and punishment translated with an introduction by David Magarshack. New York: Penguin Books, 1951, Call number: PG3326.P713 1951 (Box 34)
  - Devils (The possessed) translated with an introduction by David Magarshack. [Harmondsworth] Penguin Books Ltd., 1957, Call number: PG3326.B6 M3 (Box 35)
  - Notes from underground, White nights, the dream of a ridiculous man, and selections from the House of the dead a new translation with an afterword by Andrew R. MacAndrew. New York: New American Library, 1961, Call number: PG3326.A15 M3 1961 (Box 35)
  - Possessed a new translation by Andrew R. MacAndrew; with an afterword by Marc Slonim. New York: New American Library, 1962, Call number: PG3326.B6 1962 (Box 35)
  - Raw youth translated by Constance Garnett; introduction by Ernest J. Simmons. New York: Dell Pub. Co., 1961, Call number: PG3326.P5 1961 (Box 35)
  - Brothers Karamazov translated from the Russian by Constance Garnett. New York: Macmillan, 1948, Call number: PG3326.B7 G3 1948 (Box 58)
  - Commissioner. New York, N.Y.: Pocket Books, 1963, Call number: PS3554.O82 C65 1963 (Box 34)
  - Travels in Arabia Deserta an abridgment by Edward Garnett. Garden City, N.Y.: Doubleday, 1955, Call number: DS207.D73 1955 (Box 34)
  - Myth of Napoleon. New Haven: Yale French Studies, 1960, Call number: DC203.8.M974 1960x (Box 31)
  - Larousse's French-English, English-French dictionary. New York: Washington Square Press, 1955, Call number: PC2640.L32 1955b (Box 7)
  - Civilization of Rome. New York: New American Library, 1963, Call number: DG209.D78 1963 (Box 42)
  - Balthazar. New York: Pocket Books, Inc., 1961, Call number: PR6007.U76 B3 1961 (Box 47)
    Copy 1 in box 47, copy 2 in box 37.
  - Mountolive, a novel. New York: Dutton, 1959, Call number: PR6007.D938m 1959b (Box 17)
  - Clea. New York: Pocket Books, 1961, Call number: PR6007.U76 C5 1961 (Box 37)
  - Dark labyrinth. New York: Pocket Books, 1963, Call number: PR6007.U76 D3 1963 (Box 41)
  - Man missing. New York: Popular Library, 1964, Call number: PS3509.B453 M36 1964 (Box 37)
  - Last laugh. New York: Dell Pub. Co., 1956, Call number: PS3555.I58 L37 1956 (Box 13)
  - Day New York went dry. Greenwich, Connecticut: Fawcett Publications, Inc., 1964, Call number: PS3555.I55 D39 1964 (Box 37)
  - Mill on the floss introduction by Maxwell H. Goldberg. New York: Washington Square Press, 1961, Call number: PR4664.A1 1961 (Box 34)
  - Use of poetry and the use of criticism, studies in the relation of criticism to poetry in England Cambridge, Mass.: Harvard University Press, 1933, Call number: PN1031.E42u (Box 5)
  - Murder in the cathedral. New York: Harcourt, Brace and Company, 1935, Call number: PS3509.E42m (Box 28)
  - Waste land and other poems. New York: Harcourt, Brace and Co., 1934, Call number: PS3509.L43 W35 1934 (Box 34)
  - Confidential clerk: a play. New York: Harcourt, Brace, 1954, Call number: PS3509.L43 C69 1954 (Box 51)
  - On poetry and poets: [essays]. [New York]: Noonday Press, 1961, Call number: PN511.E435 1961 (Box 66)
  - Sacred wood: essays on poetry and criticism. London: Methuen; New York, Barnes & Noble, 1960, Call number: PN511.E42sa 1960 (Box 69)
  - Fifteen modern American poets. New York: Rinehart, 1952, Call number: PS614.E55 1952 (Box 68)
  - College book of American literature. New York: American Book Co., 1939, Call number: PS507.E65 1939 v.2 (Box 44)
  - Identity of Yeats. New York: Oxford University Press, 1964, Call number: PR5906.E47i 1964 (Box 66)
  - Trot: a novel of suspense. New York, N.Y.: New American Library, 1964, Call number: PS3555.L9 T76 1964 (Box 37)
  - Selected writings edited and with a foreword by William H. Gilman. New York: New American Library, 1965, Call number: PS1603.G42 (Box 1)
  - Milton's God William Empson. Norfolk, Conn.: New Directions, 1961, Call number: PR3592.R4E55 (Box 22)
  - 500 songs that made the all-time hit parade. New York: Bantam Books, 1964, Call number: M1628 .E57f (Box 1)
  - Poet's choice edited by Paul Engle. New York: Dial Press, 1962, Call number: PS614.E58p (Box 28)
  - Captains and the kings depart: and other stories. New York: Harper, 1949, Call number: PS3509.U66 1949 (Box 39)
  - Merchants of Venus. Greenwich, Conn.: Fawcett, 1964, Call number: PS3555.V78 M47 1964 (Box 38)
  - Short stories of James T. Farrell. Garden City, N.Y.: Halcyon House, 1941, Call number: PS3511.A738 A15 1941 (Box 5)
  - Father and son. New York: Popular Library, 1961, Call number: PS3511.A738 F37 1961 (Box 41)
  - Light in August. New York: Modern Library, 1959, Call number: PS3511.A86 L5 1959 (Box 7)
  - Absalom, Absalom! introduction by Harvey Breit. New York: Modern Library, 1951, Call number: PS3511.F27a 1951b (Box 28)
  - Sanctuary: and Requiem for a nun. [New York]: The New American Library, 1954, Call number: PS3511.A86 S3 1954 (Box 33)
  - Town. New York: Vintage Books, 1961, Call number: PS3511.A86 T6 1961 (Box 38)
  - Sound and the fury; & As I lay dying with a new appendix as a foreword by the author. New York: The Modern library, 1946, Call number: PS3511.A86 S6 1946 (Box 45)
  - William M. Gaines's The Mad sampler. New York: New American Library, 1965, Call number: NC1428.M344 1965 (Box 42)
  - History of Tom Jones, a foundling with an afterword by Frank Kermode. New York: New American Library, 1963, Call number: PR3454.H56 1963 (Box 8)
  - History of the adventures of Joseph Andrews and his friend Mr. Abraham Adams: written in imitation of the manner of Cervantes with an afterword by Irvin Ehrenpreis. New York: New American Library, 1961, Call number: PR3454.J65 1961 (Box 33)
  - Life of Mr. Jonathan Wild the Great with a foreword by J.H. Plumb. New York: New American Library, 1962, Call number: PR3454.J58 1962 (Box 45)
  - Two novels: The flower beneath the foot [and] Prancing nigger with a chronology by Miriam K. Benkovitz. [New York: New Directions], 1962, Call number: PR6011.I7 F55 1962 (Box 33)
  - Portable F. Scott Fitzgerald selected by Dorothy Parker; introduction by John O'Hara. New York: The Viking Press, 1945, Call number: PS3511.F57 A14 1945 (Box 29)
  - Tentation de saint Antoine avec introduction, notes et variantes par Edouard Maynial. Paris: Editions Garnier freres, 1954, Call number: PQ2246.T4 1954 (Box 7)
  - Madame Bovary: moeurs de province. Garden City, N.Y.: Doubleday, 1961, Call number: PQ2246.M2 1961 (Box 32)
  - Salambo. New York: Berkley Pub. Corp., 1961, Call number: PQ2246.S3 E5 1961 (Box 32)
  - Sentimental education translated, with introduction and notes, by Anthony Goldsmith. London: J. M. Dent & son ltd; New York: E. P. Dutton & co., inc., 1941, Call number: PQ2246.E2E 1941 (Box 32)
  - Madame Bovary translated by Lowell Bair; with an introduction by Malcolm Cowley. New York: Bantam, 1959, Call number: PQ2246.M2 E5s 1959 (Box 33)
  - Education sentimentale [Introduction, notes et releve de variantes par Edouard Maynial]. Paris: Garnier, 1961, Call number: PQ2246.E5 1961 (Box 34)
  - Three tales translated with an introduction by Robert Baldick. Baltimore: Penguin Books, 1961, Call number: PQ2246.T713 1961 (Box 34)
    2 copies.
  - Trois contes: Un coeur simple, La legende de saint Julien l'Hospitalier, Herodias [Introduction, notes et releve de variantes par Edouard Maynial]. Paris: Garnier freres, 1961, Call number: PQ2246.T7 1961 (Box 34)
  - Diamonds are forever. New York: New American Library, 1961, Call number: PR6056.L4 D5 1961 (Box 37)
  - Goldfinger. New York: New American Library, 1960, Call number: PR6056.L4 G6 1960 (Box 37)
  - On Her Majesty's secret service Ian Fleming. New York: New American Library, 1964, Call number: PR6056.L4 O5 1964 (Box 38)
  - Moonraker. New York: New American Library, 1960, Call number: PR6056.L4 M66 1960 (Box 48)
  - In the red. New York: Lancer Books, 1964, Call number: PR6011.L46 I6 1964 (Box 37)
  - All good men. New York, N.Y.: Macfadden-Bartell, 1964, Call number: PS3556.L45 A55 1964 (Box 47)
  - And presumed dead. Toronto; New York: Bantam, 1964, Call number: PS3556.L424 A84 1964 (Box 47)
  - Blindfold. New York: Bantam Books, 1961, Call number: PS3556.L424 B5 1961 (Box 47)
  - Pocket history of American painting. New York: Washington Square Press, 1962, Call number: ND205.F54 1962 (Box 47)
  - Franz Kafka today. Madison: University of Wisconsin Press, 1962, Call number: PT2621.A26 Z69 1962 (Box 32)
  - Anthology of French poetry from Nerval to Valery in English translation. Garden City, N.Y.: Doubleday, 1958, Call number: PQ1170.E6 F5 1958 (Box 38)
  - Portraits from life: memories and criticism of Henry James, Joseph Conrad, Thomas Hardy, H.G. Wells, Stephen Crane, D.H. Lawrence, John Galsworthy, Ivan Turgenev, W.H. Hudson, Theodore Dreiser, A. C. Swinburne Ford Madox Ford. Chicago: H. Regnery, 1937, Call number: PR473.F64 1937 (Box 33)
  - Aspects of the novel. New York: Harcourt Brace & World, 1954, Call number: PN3358.F6 1954 (Box 32)
  - Abinger harvest New York, N.Y.: Meridian, 1955, Call number: PR6011.O58 A63 1955 (Box 55)
  - Penguin book of German verse: with plain prose translations of each poem. [Baltimore]: Penguin Books, 1957, Call number: PT1155.F6 (Box 32)
  - Collector. New York, N.Y.: Dell Pub. Co., 1964, Call number: PR6056.O85 C6 1964 (Box 37)
  - Mallarme with fourteen line drawings by Henri Matisse. [Chicago]: University of Chicago Press, 1962, Call number: PQ2344.Z5 F8 1962 (Box 32)
  - Mid-century French poets; selections, translations, and critical notices. New York: Grove Press, 1955, Call number: PQ1184.F6 1955a (Box 33)
  - Age of surrealism. [New York]: Swallow Press, 1950, Call number: BH301.S75 F6 1950 (Box 59)
  - Alcoholism: its scope, cause, and treatment. New York: Random House, 1955, Call number: RC565.F65 1955 (Box 45)
  - Queen Pedauque translated by Jos. A. V. Stritzko; introduction by James Branch Cabell. New York: Modern Library, 1923, Call number: PQ2254.R7E 1923 (Box 20)
  - Ezra Pound. New York: Grove Press, 1961, Call number: PS3531.O82 Z63 1961 (Box 42)
  - Wall-to-wall trap. New York, N.Y.: MacFadden-Bartell, 194, Call number: PS3513.O155 W35 1964 (Box 42)
  - Mr. Cat: drawings. New York: H. Frisch, 1960, Call number: QL795.C2 F87 (Box 29)
  - Because of the cats. New York: Ballantine Books, 1965, Call number: PR6056.R4 B4 1965 (Box 37)
  - Greek city-states. New York: Norton, 1963, Call number: DF82.F68 1963 (Box 51)
  - Group psychology and the analysis of the ego authorized translation by James Strachey. London: Hogarth Press, 1948, Call number: BF173.G76 1948 (Box 18)
  - On creativity and the unconscious; papers on the psychology of art, literature, love, religion selected, with introduction and annotations, by Benjamin Nelson. New York: Harper, 1958, Call number: BF173.F89on (Box 33)
  - Collected papers. Vol. II authorized translation under the supervision of Joan Riviere. London: Hogarth Press: Institute of Psycho-Analysis, 1964, Call number: BF173.F89 1942 v.2 (Box 44)
  - Modern poetry, American and British. New York: Appleton-Century-Crofts, 1951, Call number: PR1225.F91m (Box 29)
  - Feminine mystique. New York, N.Y: Dell, 1964, Call number: HQ1420.F7 1964 (Box 38)
  - Landscape, portrait, still-life; their origin and development. [Translated from the German by R.F.C. Hull] New York: Schocken Books, 1963, Call number: ND1150.F91eE 1963 (Box 32)
  - Old masters of Belgium & Holland introduction by Meyer Schapiro; [translated by Mary C. Robbins]. New York: Schocken Books, 1963, Call number: ND631.F913 1963 (Box 41)
  - In the clearing. New York: Holt, Rinehart and Winston, 1962, Call number: PS3511.F92i (Box 18)
  - Pocket book of Robert Frost's poems with an introduction and commentary by Louis Untermeyer. [New York: Pocket Books Inc.], 1956, Call number: PS3511.R94 A6 1956 (Box 32)
  - T.S. Eliot. New York: Grove Press, 1963, Call number: PS3509.L43 Z674 1963 (Box 32)
  - Time right deadly. New York: Collier, 1962, Call number: PR6057.A34 T55 1962 (Box 37)
  - Answer to heaven. New York: Avon Books, a division of the Hearst Corporation, 1962, Call number: PS3557.A344 A5 1962 (Box 38)
  - Planet called earth. New York: Bantam Books, 1965, Call number: QE501.G36 1965 (Box 37)
  - Poet in New York: complete Spanish text with a new translation by Ben Belitt; introduction by Angel del Rio. New York: Grove Press, 1955, Call number: PQ6613.A67 P7 1955 (Box 69)
  - Art of T. S. Eliot. New York: Dutton., 1959, Call number: PS3509.E42 G2 1959 (Box 32)
  - Galloway case. New York: Lancer Books, 1964, Call number: PR6073.I56 G34 1964 (Box 40)
  - Concise history of English painting. New York: Praeger, 1964, Call number: ND461.G3 (Box 32)
  - Dante Alighieri: three lectures. Washington: Published for the Library of Congress by the Gertrude Clarke Whittall Poetry and Literature Fund; [for sale by the Superintendent of Documents, U.S. Govt. Print. Off.]., 1965, Call number: PQ4363.B65 U58 (Box 18)
  - American poetry at mid-century by John Crowe Ransom, Delmore Schwartz and John Hall Wheelock; lectures presented under the auspices of the Gertrude Whittall Poetry and Literature Fund. Washington: Reference Dept., Library of Congress, 1958, Call number: PS324.U55 1958 (Box 37)
    Schwartz, pp.15-31.
  - Decline and fall of the Roman Empire: and other selected writings edited and abridged with an introduction by Hugh R. Trevor-Roper. New York: Washington Square Press, 1963, Call number: DG311.G55 1963a (Box 33)
  - Gibbon's The decline and fall of the Roman Empire a modern abridgement by Moses Hadas. Greenwich, Conn.: Fawcett, 1964, Call number: DG311.G5 1964 (Box 33)
  - Trial: a dramatization based on Franz Kafka's novel translated by Leon Katz. New York: Schocken Books, 1963, Call number: PQ2613.G36 P92E 1963 (Box 32)
  - Counterfeiters: with Journal of The counterfeiters the novel translated from the French by Dorothy Bussy; the journal translated from the French and annotated by Justin O'Brien. New York: Modern Library, 1955, Call number: PQ2613.I2 F3813 1955 (Box 28)
  - Lafcadio's adventures translated from the French by Dorothy Bussy. New York: Vintage Books, 1953, Call number: PQ2613.G36 C3E 1953 (Box 43)
  - Two legends: Oedipus and Theseus translated from the French by John Russell. New York: Vintage Books, 1950, Call number: PQ2613.I2 O42 1950 (Box 43)
  - James Joyce's Ulysses: a study. New York: Vintage Books, 1955, Call number: PR6019.O9 U65 1955 (Box 45)
  - Painting and reality Etienne Gilson. New York: Meridan Books, 1955, Call number: ND1150.G42 1959b (Box 33)
  - Kaddish, and other poems, 1958-1960. [San Francisco]: City Lights Books, 1961, Call number: PS3513.I74 K3 1961 (Box 54)
  - Proust: a collection of critical essays edited by Rene Girard. Englewood Cliffs, N.J.: Prentice-Hall, 1962, Call number: PQ2631.P94 Z5gi (Box 66)
  - Flaubert; a collection of critical essays. Englewood Cliffs, N.J.: Prentice-Hall, 1964, Call number: PQ2249.G44f (Box 33)
  - Intermezzo: comedie en trois actes. [Paris]: Grasset, 1964, Call number: PQ2613.I74 I6 1964 (Box 8)
  - Sodome et Gomorrhe: piece en deux actes frontispiece de Christian Berard. Paris: Bernard Grasset, 1951, Call number: PQ2613.G44 S6 1951 (Box 33)
  - Three plays translated by Phyllis la Farge with Peter H. Judd. New York: Hill and Wang, 1964, Call number: PQ2613.I74 T43 1964 (Box 40)
  - Guerre de Troie n'aura pas lieu: piece en deux actes. Paris: B. Grasset, 1935, Call number: PQ2613.I74 G8 1935 (Box 41)
  - Bella: histoire des fontranges. Paris: B. Grasset, 1926, Call number: PQ2613.I74 B4 1926 (Box 55)
  - Ancient world: a beginning. Baltimore: Penguin Books, 1944, Call number: D59.G56 1944 (Box 41)
  - Married woman: a Jean-Luc Godard film text based on the English subtitles of Ursule Molinaro; essay on the film by Tom Milne. New York: Berkley Publishing Corp., 1965, Call number: PN1997.J826E (Box 8)
  - Faust: eine Tragodie: erster und zweiter Teil. Munchen: Goldmann, 1962, Call number: PT1919.A1 1962 (Box 33)
  - Sufferings of young Werther = Die Leiden des jungen Werther edited by Harry Steinhauer; with a translation, critical introduction, notes and vocabulary by the editor. New York: Bantam Books, 1962, Call number: PT2027.W3 S7 1962 (Box 40)
  - Goethe: with plain prose translations of each poem introduced and edited by David Luke. Harmondsworth, Middlesex, England; New York, N.Y., U.S.A.: Penguin Books, 1964, Call number: PT2026.A3 L84 1964 (Box 42)
  - West-ostlicher Divan: Noten und Abhandlungen zu besserem Verstandnis des West-ostlichen Divans Johann Wolfgang Goethe; Bearbeitet von Kurt Waselowsky. Munchen: W. Goldmann Verlag, 1958, Call number: PT1898.W4 1958 (Box 43)
  - Dead souls a new translation by Andrew R. MacAndrew; with a foreword by Frank O'Connor. [New York]: New American Library, 1961, Call number: PG3333.M4 1961 (Box 67)
  - Diary of a madman and other stories newly translated by Andrew R. McAndrew; with an afterword by Leon Stilman. [New York]: New American Library, 1961, Call number: PG3333.Z3 1961 (Box 67)
  - Love & like. New York: Dial Press, 1960, Call number: PS3557.G558I 1960 (Box 45)
  - Therefore be bold: a novel. New York: Dial Press, 1960, Call number: PS3557.O34 1960 (Box 51)
  - James Joyce. New York: Grove Press, 1962, Call number: PR6019.O9 Z538 1962 (Box 23)
  - Your turn to curtsy my turn to bow. New York: Bantam Books, 1960, Call number: PS3557.O384 Y6 1960 (Box 23)
  - Temple of gold. New York: Bantam Books, 1958, Call number: PS3557.O384 1958 (Box 47)
  - Vicar of Wakefield with an afterword by J.H. Plumb. New York: New American Library, 1961, Call number: PR3490.A1 1961 (Box 40)
  - Oblomov a new translation by Ann Dunnigan; With a foreword by Harry T. Moore. [New York]: New American Library, 1963, Call number: PG3337.G6oE 1963 (Box 67)
  - Goncourt journals, 1851-1870 edited and translated from the Journal of Edmond and Jules de Goncourt, with an introduction, notes, and a biographical repertory by Lewis Galantiere. Garden City, N.Y.: Doubleday, 1958, Call number: PQ2261.Z5 A225 1958 (Box 40)
  - Experiment in terror. New York: Bantam Books, 1962, Call number: PS3557.O67 O74 1962 (Box 42)
  - Menace by the Gordons. New York: Bantam Books, 1964, Call number: PS3557.O67 M46 1964 (Box 42)
  - Murder rides the campaign train by the Gordons. New York: Popular Library, 1952, Call number: PS3557.O665 M8 (Box 48)
  - Fall of a titan translated from the Russian by Mervyn Black. New York: Popular Library, 1964, Call number: PG3476.G6542 F23 1964 (Box 42)
  - How to draw the human figure with an introduction by Henry Gasser. New York: Dell, 1958, Call number: NC765.G73 1958 (Box 42)
  - Myths of the Greeks and Romans. New York: New American Library, 1964, Call number: BL722.G7 1964 (Box 25)
  - Tin drum [Translated from the German by Ralph Manheim]. Greenwich, Conn.: Fawcett, 1964, Call number: PT2613.R338 B55 1964 (Box 47)
  - Claudius, the god and his wife Messalina: the troublesome reign of Tiberius Claudius Caesar, Emperor of the Romans (born 10 B.C., died A.D. 54), as described by himself; also his murder at the hands of the notorious Agrippina (mother of the Emperor Nero Harmondsworth: Penguin Books, 1954, Call number: PR6013.R35 C6 1954 (Box 8)
  - I, Claudius: from the autobiography of Tiberius Claudius, born B.C. X, murdered and deified A.D. LIV. New York: Vintage Books, 1961, Call number: PR6013.R35 I35 1961 (Box 25)
  - Mind of Proust: a detailed interpretation of A la recherche du temps perdu. Cambridge [Eng.]: University Press, 1949, Call number: PQ2631.P94 Z5g (Box 22)
  - Great world: portraits and scenes from Greville's memoirs, 1814-1860 edited with an introduction by Louis Kronenberger. Garden City, N.Y.: Anchor Books, 1964, Call number: DA536.G8 A423 1964 (Box 17)
  - Second man. New York: Dell, 1964, Call number: PR6013.R72 S4 1964 (Box 47)
  - Movies: the sixty-year story of the world of Hollywood and its effect on America, from pre-nickelodeon days to the present. New York: Bonanza Books, 1957, Call number: PN1993.5.U5 G87 1957 (Box 2)
  - Personal voice: a contemporary prose reader. Philadelphia: Lippincott, 1964, Call number: PE1122.G8 (Box 29)
  - Location of things collage by Robert Goodnough. New York: Tibor de Nagy Editions, 1960, Call number: PS3513.U44 L6 1960 (Box 44)
  - Graffiti [poems]. New York: Macmillan, 1959, Call number: PS3513.G98g (Box 23)